The world's destroyed
before it becomes beautiful.
This is the world I envisioned.
This is how the world
should have been.
But in this world...
Only my body is rotting.
Becoming decayed.
Maybe this is how
I should have been.
Maybe this was my true self.
But then finally, I remember...
That I am still only
a junior high student...
That I wasn't
thinking about anything...
And that nothing amazing
has ever happened here...
Hold it right there.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Before you come downstairs,
say "Good Morning!"
So let's give it another go!
Three, two...
Your tsundere persona is getting
polished every day, Hidomi-chan.
I understand there are
customers who come for that...
...but I'm your mom after all.
What about breakfast?
I can add this week's special
with the usual morning set.
Sauteed natto.
I don't want any.
Yeah? Then have a good day.
But before you go. Three, two...
Good morning, Mommy.
Good morning!
Morning, Hidomi!
Morning...
Nothing'll come out if you keep
teasing it endlessly like that.
She knew that and kept
swirling, twirling, whirling...
And I was in
heaven for eternity...
You okay, Ide-kun?
So what happened
to you yesterday, Ide?
Huh? Yesterday, you ask?
That teacher spent the night at
your place, right? What happened?
Well, I'll leave that
to your imagination.
Wow!
For reals? Seriously?
Congratulations, I guess.
Well, yeah...
It's real?
Oh yeah. What was the "secret
plan" you mentioned yesterday?
Oh, that.
What's that?
Art gallery.
Art gallery?
For reals?
Women are suckers for
these things. Got it, boys?
You seem to have
a different persona, Ide.
It's not about my character...
Looking at art and thinking about
the world we live in. The universe?
Scrutinize it? Peek in from a gap?
I'm interested in the philosophical...
You're not interested in that.
That's not true! Well, honestly I'm
not interested in fine art like this...
...but look. If we go see
a beautiful night scene like this...
...we could
deepen our relationship.
Relationship!
Wow...
Ide... Ide... Why you, Ide...
When are you pulling
the trigger on your relationship?
What are we talking about?
Your grown-up art gallery...
Mori-kun, let's not talk about that.
Huh?
Why don't we talk about
your fashion sense today?
What about it?
What's with your style?
This is unisex. Right, Marco?
This is totally unisex, right?
I guess so...
What's unisex?
You're so outdated. If you bring
gender into fashion these days...
...they'll lock you in a nursing home!
Really?
That's right. Plenty of
guys wear skirts nowadays.
Do they, Marco? Can old farts...
...who look like they sleep
on benches till dawn wear skirts?
Who's an old fart?
I think anyone can
wear whatever they like.
Right? That's the truth!
Fine, just quit
showing your underwear.
I'm not showing it to you.
You're the one looking.
I'm not trying to, but I can see it.
Anyone instinctively would.
Right, Marco?
I guess.
You don't need
to look at my panties.
They're briefs, not panties.
Because you can look at Miss
Shimazaki's panties all you want!
What are you saying!
Don't be stupid! You're so dumb!
Good morning.
Please repeat after me.
Sit down.
We're already sitting.
Marvelous.
Full house then.
For today's subject,
I'd like ask you, today's youth...
...who are starting
an understandably regrettable day.
Yeah, he's wearing a uniform
Why a uniform?
No other boy would wear a uniform
Really? Couldn't be
I'm serious I saw him
Did you get a good look? Not just a glance
That bag! It has to be!
Bag, haha! That's hilarious
I know, right!
Awesome if true
So weird
What about his hands?
I only saw his face
What is the most important thing
for you, society's weakest links?
You over there.
I don't know.
Correct.
I saw Miss Shima come out of a run-down apartment
Then Ide came out
How old is Miss Shima
Really old
Did she spend the night at Ide's?
So he's lost his virginity?!
(>m<)
Whoa...
He'll stop acting like a virgin now
I bet he called her teacher~!
Or Miss Shima! haha
Ugh, doing it with a teacher is so gross
Well, Miss Shima's so plain lol
They make a good couple lol
It's been one week since I was
assigned to this class. That is all...
...I want to teach you.
Now we'll begin
the lesson plan.
Teacher...
We shouldn't do this...
This is wrong...
Teacher....
T-Teacher... Teacher... T...
I'm going to get in trouble...
I'm gonna get in trouble!
Teacher, I can't...
Look at this... It's so big...
T-Teacher...
What's she making her watch?
From the audio... It's bad.
Real naughty.
Next.
You could react a little.
You don't want to hit adolescence
when you're over the hill.
Okay, we've had enough here.
Who's next?
Me!
Oh, I don't need to test you, Ide-kun.
Who's next?
Me!
Mori, what do you see?
It's...
What is this?
Princess, may I have a napkin?
Is my avocado
parfait ready yet?
Hidomi-chan,
I'd like more coffee please.
Princess is best like that...
I love it when she looks
down at us with those eyes.
Same here.
You're on fire, princess. You have
what it takes to be a champ...
Thanks, Hidomi-chan.
I couldn't have done it without you.
But I guess I need
to hire someone soon.
I shouldn't waste your valuable
time with helping out at the cafe.
The plant here is the same.
Even the sound it makes.
I wonder where he is now?
I've been thinking lately...
Maybe it's time we stop
waiting for him in this city.
Sorry. I shouldn't say things
like this. But you're now...
Mommy. You know what?
Hidomi-chan!
That was a close one, ma'am.
She was about to overflow.
Overflow?
Strange.
I thought it was a fatal hit.
Fatal hit?
Unfortunately, ma'am, your
daughter is completely fine.
That's unfortunate?
Hidomi-chan!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Hey, that's mine!
Nothing's playing.
Give it back!
Where did you buy this?
It's not something anyone can get.
This...
Someone gave this to me.
You should keep it off.
It doesn't suit you.
Pretending not to hear.
That's your thing, right?
When you're paused like that,
your body will just rot away.
Is that what you want to become?
W-Wait a minute!
I will take full responsibility for
your daughter retaining her life.
Oh. By the way.
Be careful of
the woman on the Vespa.
Hidomi-chan!
Did you see her plate numbers?
It's a hit and run! Don't be
an irresponsible adult like that!
What is... with her?
But she was kinda cool...
What?
There's nothing I want to be.
There's nothing I want to do.
There isn't an image I want to be.
I have nothing.
All that's there is... zero.
W-What is this!
Hidomi-chan?
Hidomi-chan!
Mom...
Hibajiri-san?
Um... Ide-kun?
It's starting to move!
What is that?
I don't know either.
I was walking home and...
This late?
It came out of nowhere.
From where?
F-From my head.
We should be safe here...
Dammit! What's going on?
N-No!
Dammit!
I see. Now I get it.
Hey! Where's the one
who pulled that out of you?
Answer me! You were hit.
By the woman on a Vespa!
Ves...pa?
U-Um...
Who are you?
What about Ide-kun?
I'm going to take care of his
wounds. You should head home.
Hey, wait!
Oh, by the way.
That looks good on you.
Well, I'm glad nothing
happened to you, Hidomi-chan.
I was worried you
ran away from home.
But if you're going to run
away, do it with a bang.
Just don't break
the house next time.
W-Why?
She said she'll take responsibility
for yesterday. Introduce yourself.
The name's Jinyu.
Ide! What's with
all those bandages?
What happened?
Well, a lot happened.
A lot of things.
Lots of things?
Today, as you start a disastrous
day as modern-day youth...
...I, as the clear structural winner
in life, would like to present you...
Takeshi likes Emily, right?
For real?!
Really?!
I didn't know that!
Then he's free now!
Chance!!
Go!!
You'll never get a chance like this again!!
Go with the flow
Huh?
You mean me?!
You'll do it, right?
...very important banter on
how to live in this universe.
You there.
Ah.
Correct.
She's free, after all
Huh?
Yeah, fair game hah
Free!
Hang on!
Don't say you're not interested now!
What'll it be Take-chan!
You guys...
You've gotta do
You'd better do it!
She'll never be free like this again!
Yep
She's free, good and free!
Free flee! flee free
Free fooly
Fooly free?
Fooly cooly?
...I know those who live contently by
fulfilling animalistic sexual urges...
I gave so, so much,
but there was little output.
I have no use for
a piece-of-scum bug...
Fooly... cooly...
I don't want all of you
to be that non-existent youth.
I want all of you to become
adults of cosmological scale!
You've gotta do
You'd better do it!
She'll never be free like this again!
Yep
She's free, good and free!
Free flee! flee free
Free fooly
Fooly free?
Fooly cooly?
Fooly cooly??
Fooly cooly???
Fooly cooly ヽ(°0°*)?
Fooly cooly
Fooly cooly!!?
FLCL
Fooly cooly!!!!!
fooly cooly
FL--CL--
Fooly cooly
flcl!
You don't need wings to go
venture out into the universe.
Who would ride
a four-wheeled car with wings?
You must not become
that kind of adult.
You do not need four wheels.
You only need two!
As loaches gather
underneath a willow tree!
There is a lot of gravity underneath
all of you! You must conquer it!
Fooly cooly???
Fooly cooly ヽ(°0°*)?
Fooly cooly
Fooly cooly!!?
FLCL
Fooly cooly!!!!!
fooly cooly
FL--CL--
Fooly cooly
flcl!
Fooly! Cooly!
FLCLFLCLFLCL
Fooly cooly!
Fooly cooly!!
FLCL!!Fooly cooly!
FLCL
Fooolyycooolyy
fooly cooly!
Fooly!! Cooly!!!
Fooly cooly fooly cooly
Fooly! Cooly!
FLCL
Fooly coooly
Fooly Cooly fooly cooly
F!L!C!L!
Fooly cooly -ly-
FLCL !
Fooly!! Cooly!!!!
Fooly cooly Fooly cooly
Fooly! Cooly!
Stand up, youth!
Do whatever you want!
As least adequate as you can
possibly be! Completely sloppily!
Born to be mild!
Finally, the real one appears.
"Bow wow!" You can't
bark like that anymore.
Because everything on
this planet is burned and crushed.
Humans are dead and stinking!
And the doggie is "nom,
nom, nom" like it's a feast.
Now isn't food important after all?
Because you are what you eat.
So when someone eats something
they shouldn't, what happens?
Well, that person becomes
something they're not, meaning...
Oh, here he comes.
He's so cute.
Is he searching for something?
Oh, it appears he smells something.
Oh, this one's adorable too.
Cameraman, please zoom in.
I can't read their expression,
so I'm not sure how they feel.
But that's what's
so cute about them.
Oh! Fantastic!
Unlike their delightful
entrance, that's savage!
Thank you, world!
I am devoured once again today,
totally and neatly split open.
And I finally remember.
That I wasn't thinking about anything.
That we're on planet Earth and...
We're on planet Earth and...
What was I saying?
maid
No!
Mixy-mixy curry rice needs to be
mixed in front of the customer...
...so don't mix it beforehand!
Oh. Good morning, Hidomi-chan.
Hidomi, be careful
of the Vespa woman...
Next, bittersweet
unrequited love parfait!
Have a nice day.
Thanks.
Hidomi! The Vespa woman...
Hello! It's Miss Haruko!
The world is
overflowing irresponsibly.
Wherever you look, there
are many who defile others...
...and their surroundings
with selfish delusions.
And I believe this is the fault of the
adults of this world, including me.
I'm so sorry.
I'm no longer able to think that way. Pupipi.
Even if I think of this planet...
A mole I didn't notice before...
Or the hair that grows out of it.
I keep thinking about those things.
World. Universe.
I really don't care.
It's not my fault
anyway. Pu-pu-pu.
Pu-pu-pu...
Pu-pi-pu.
Pu-pi-pu...
Miss Haruko! Miss Haruko!
You are good kids.
Well, I'm hungry, so the rest
of class is self-study time.
And the class album is
finished now, so please take a look.
An album?
Oh! I remember Sports Day...
Yeah, it was epic.
Miss Haruko's wicked pitch where
she lets them hit to get an easy out.
Miss Haruko's last round full base
comeback line drive to the pitcher...
- It was awesome.
- Legendary!
It was so fun...
After-School UFO!
We signaled a UFO after school and
invited an esper to the cultural fair.
During the spoon-bending contest,
she bent her foe's fingers and won!
We used the school building
to make a bonfire at the after party.
Campfire
- Burn, burn, burn.
- These are all great memories.
- Flames, burn bright.
- This class is the best.
Yes, we are blessed.
Flare up the tinders.
And burn into the sky too!
Hibaji.
Can you deliver this?
For Ide. Since he's absent today.
But why me?
I don't know.
Why is it?
Because you're close? Huh?
Why?
I don't know.
Thanks!
Mom, this place is boring.
It sure is outdated looking.
What is this?
He's so big!
He's really hard!
How long do I need to work?
Hey, princess.
What are you doing here?
Oh, it's you...
Princess, do you want to become a pro?
You can do it. You'd be a phenomenon...
She won't be a pro!
Leave her alone, sir.
You have Latin blood in you, eh?
Um, yes.
Do you want to become a pro?
You can do it.
You'd be a phenomenon...
Sir, there aren't lots of
phenomena lying around.
Let's go.
You have a fine fist. You sure
you don't want to become a pro?
What kind?
Uh, let's see...
You're delivering a worksheet to Ide?
Yeah.
This isn't a place
a woman should come alone.
Hibajiri, are you sure you
want to see the real Ide?
What do you mean?
Well, you're going to see
it even if you say no.
Look.
Hey! Keep it moving!
You've got no grit, you fools!
Sir, yes, sir!
Who do you think feeds
you good-for-nothings?
Look at that body unsuited
for a middle schooler!
That beautiful, sculpted body that
is comparable but superior to mine!
Get working, you brat!
Yes, sir!
He pretends to be the class
clown and acts dumb at school...
...but he's actually
struggling to make ends meet.
That's enough.
Now go get another one!
He wouldn't show that side
of himself to any of us though.
Yes, sir!
You there! Keep your feet moving!
Look at these bargains!
Ide's Factory
These are high-performance custom
weapons made by this genius!
This one's an automatic machine
gun that can shoot 100 pebbles!
You can use pebbles that are
exactly 5 mm! It's very versatile!
If you think, "I can't
find pebbles in that size..."
...then I have this item for you!
This Super Eccentric
Almighty Pulverization Machine...
...can crush rocks into
5 mm pebbles in seconds!
You can't carry
something like this around?
For those who need help
lugging this stuff, I have this!
A 100-shot pebble machine gun...
...Pebble Super Eccentric Almighty
Pulverization Machine Cart!
As you can see...
You wanna give it a try? All right.
Give it a go, tough guy!
- Hey! Stop it! Stop it! Ack!
- Stop it.
That means to stop...
He's fluent in those kinds of
English words! It breaks my heart!
You call this trash a gun?
Are you fucking kidding me?
How am I supposed to kill
someone with it? Huh?
I don't need this shit!
Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
Shut up!
Should I knock you down, punk?
Sorry, I don't feel any pain in my heart,
however many punches I get.
Gah! It really hurts! Sorry, it really hurts.
Please stop! it really hurts!
Nerds.
Hey!
Mori... Hibajiri-san?
Hibajiri-san!
Hibajiri-san? Hey...
Why is it always him?
Koh-kun, I made
tsukudani for you...
Oh my. You brought
another girl home?
Oh, you dirty dog! So bad!
Oh, to be young.
You know, when I was young...
No!
Sobby... I'b okay.
Okay...
Oh, right. Hibajiri-san. Um...
Interested in space?
Um, like art? The universe?
Like an art gallery?
A relationship kind of like
these stars, this nighttime scenery.
No, no, no. Nothing suggestive
like that, a pure companionship?
Relationship? No no, that's not it!
I'm sorry.
Excuse me?
Thanks.
Um, sure.
I guess...
If it were with you,
I'd be fine with it.
That kind of relationship.
Cut!
Ide, that was perfect!
Are you aiming for an Oscar?
When did you get here?
Miss Haruko?
Let's take a short break! Rolling
the final take next! Final take...
Hehehe.
Hiba... Hiba... Hibajiri!
Don't be so rough...
Cut it out!
I found you.
Let me go to
the bathroom in peace.
What's going on?
Who is she? A thief?
No! She's...
Who are you again?
You can't pretend you
forgot me, Haruha Raharu.
Answering machine.
You can't escape from me.
Namamugi, namagome, namanamako.
It's fate we meet again.
I'm going to end this.
Ape. Oh, I lose.
You're playing shiritori?
Fine, I understand.
Then we'll do this by force!
Oh, that's how you do things?
This is between us.
Don't lay your hands on her.
But it's fine to use that big hand?
Hibajiri-san!
Laser beam!
I won't let you escape.
Ide-kun!
Take that!
You had it tough too... Huh?
Hello?
Oh, Hidomi's mother. Sorry, I'm...
I told you that a "Maid Delivery
Purine la Mode" is our special menu.
I'm in a middle of something!
Will you repeat your mistake? There's
no light at the end of this tunnel.
Give it up.
No way!
Full-base comeback
line drive to the pitcher!
Play ball!
You said it was a comeback hit!
You're not going
to reach him like this!
Raharu!
You can't do it alone.
You can't reach him without me.
Such self-confidence.
You already know this...
because you're me!
One, ten, hundred, thousand!
They call me Flaming Slugger!
Hidomi. I warned you not
to get involved with that woman.
She'll only use you.
Worst case, you could die.
Die?
Hidomi?
Hidomi!
It can't be... She overcame the
enzyme inhibitory mechanism?
Sex drive?
Huh?
What's that?
You're looking good.
Sexual harrassment?
Hidomi!
What?
Hidomi! Hidomi!
Ide-kun...
Don't worry.
You'll recover in a few hours.
You exceeded expectations...
Hold it right there!
No matter how you
look at it, that girl's mine.
You look awful.
Worksheet. You were absent today.
W-W-Where did she come from?
Hidomi-chan is here!
We'll devour each other
today! With my friends!
Friends who are former
classmates I never talked to!
Hooray!
Hey... what?
Oh no! No one's here!
I want to feel
the pain of being eaten!
This one layer of skin that divides
my body's insides and outsides...
I want it peeled off, gnawed off...
I want it ripped
open with one strike!
The cold air I feel on my broken
skin is the temperature of the world!
Hidomi! Hidomi!
I told you to watch out
for the Vespa woman.
I told you to be careful.
Why didn't you listen?
Wow!
I-I can't handle this...
Wow...
Miss Haruko, you're the best...
Hey, students.
Any of you want to put sunscreen on me?
Yes, ma'am!
Wait.
Mori-kun, look at the time.
Isn't your girlfriend coming soon?
You invited us to the beach
because you have a new girlfriend.
You better introduce us.
That's right!
That's right, my friends!
Oh, look at the time.
Follow me, men!
Fine. You'll do, Hibaji.
I'm fine with you too, Jinyu.
Comrades!
This is my girlfriend, Aiko-chan.
C'mon, say something.
Um, I'm Aiko.
I'm dating your friend Mori-kun...
How embarrassing!
Even on a hot day like this,
this pretty girl doesn't sweat.
Say, may I ask why you
decided to date Mori?
U-Um... Because I like him...
This is embarrassing.
What's that you're holding?
Oh this? This is a flower pot.
Why do you carry a flower pot?
It helps me relax.
Relax...
Isn't she cute?
I'm embarrassed...
It may not look like it,
but it's quite expensive.
Oh yeah?
I wouldn't have guessed...
She's so cute...
Hey, what SPF is this?
Suntan?
Hey!
You holding a grudge?
The last three months...
You've been chasing
after me. This is nothing.
You got what you wanted once before.
It's time to quit.
No way. I want
my wish to fulfill me.
How embarrassing!
Attack, Number One!
Let's call a truce for now.
Let me join you.
That woman...
What's her objective?
The same as mine.
Receive!
Pu-pu-pu! Keep going!
Then, Jinyu...
What do you want to do?
I was with someone amazing.
He's big and strong,
just straight-out amazing.
With him, you can fly
around anywhere in space.
But he suddenly disappeared.
He abandoned me.
In the end, I wasn't his equal.
I'm not enough for him by myself.
But we continue to look for him.
We?
Miss Haruko too?
You chase it since
you can't catch it.
Want to touch it
since you can't reach it.
You must have something like that.
Me?
What does Hidomi want?
There's nothing I want to do.
Receive!
I want to see you next, Mori-kun.
Blue spring... So nice.
As an extension of our friendship?
A delayed Spring?
I'm content if you've
changed your mind.
Either way, you can't have Hidomi.
There's no point in fighting anymore.
What? I didn't know that.
Brainwashing-type suppression mechanism...
They took measures.
By the way...
What's so fun about this?
Oh, I need to pee.
I gotta go! I gotta go!
You're not going to swim?
What?
No...
Okay? Even though we're here to swim?
What about you?
Yes?
Did you bring your swimsuit?
That's not part of the plan this time.
Did you see that? Did you?
Aiko-chan, did you
see my awesomeness?
Hey. Where's Hibajiri?
I can't find her.
I wonder where she went.
Miss Haruko's gone too.
Maybe they headed home.
What if they didn't?
We should look again!
Mori-kun.
Aiko needs to go home soon.
Oh yeah. That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm walking her to the station.
O-Okay.
Thanks.
You're very sweet, Mori-kun.
It's no big deal.
Hey. I went overtime.
I'm sorry.
Well?
Oh, right.
Hold this.
Sure.
Did I play the character
like you wanted?
Yes, it was perfect!
You were great!
The train is leaving shortly.
The exact amount.
You boys think it's cute when
girls play shy and timid, right?
Oh, you can have that.
It's a gift.
W-Wow. Thank yo...
Of course not.
Let's pretend that we
exchanged this with that.
I'd be in trouble if people find
out I'm a girlfriend for rent.
"I bought this."
Okay, bye.
Marco!
As a kid...
Who is it?
...did you try and fail
to draw a picture...
...of seeing fireworks
with your family?
Is this Jinyu?
Where's Hidomi...
I mean, isn't Hibajiri with you?
You try to draw
countless specks of light...
...but the only way to fill in the
night sky is with black colored pencil.
They were lighting up the sky.
They were so colorful and beautiful.
I don't get this! What are you saying?
All beautiful things disappear.
Oh, the first star.
Please stop.
Let's get to know each other...
Stop...
Is it here?
No... Stop. Please.
Uri-uri-uri...
Just laugh.
Don't laugh!
Oh my. You were
planning on having fun today.
Tell me. Where do
I hit you to overflow?
Overflow?
What are you doing, Miss Haruko?
What? It's coming out of that one?
I don't know what you are, but...
Save Hibajiri!
It's too painful to watch, Mori-kun!
Stop crying. You're making
me feel more pathetic.
I don't know...
Aiko. Do you know what happened
to the flower pot that was here?
I dunno.
Hey there. This is
code name Eye Patch.
I have a slight problem.
What's wrong?
I can't locate the "flower pot."
Dammit!
Hidomi...
Ow...
You're the only one
who can save Hidomi, Ide.
Over here.
What happened to you?
Never mind. We need
to take care of that.
Hidomi is inside of that thing!
That's not normal, right?
No, there was plenty
that wasn't normal lately...
...but that's unacceptable!
Please! Do something, Jinyu!
If you can't draw fireworks...
Try shooting one in the air.
Do it again.
As many times as needed!
No. Instead,
you should be the firework.
Wow! This is amazing!
I got you now!
Hey! Hibajiri!
Hibajiri! Hibajiri!
Dammit. What can I do?
Mm, she doesn't have enough yet.
Miss Haruko...
Episodic drama?
Tsun-dora?
Tsundere?
This girl has those
qualities, doesn't she?
Shut up.
Hibajiri!
Hibajiri! Hibajiri!
Wake up...
Calling her name won't help.
Leave it to teacher.
Stop it!
Then take off her headphones.
Your voice will reach her.
Don't be tricked, Ide! Don't remove...
You can reach it...
Deep inside of her.
So let's do it together.
I can do it myself!
Hibajiri! Hibajiri!
Dammit!
I said to stop it! That's...
The emergency
system has been activated.
There's nothing you can do.
Jeez. Those sneaky bastards.
It's because you tried to tempt him.
T-That's right! You tried to...
Hibajiri!
Wh...
Where did she come from?
It's Hidomi-chan...
Hey! Hibajiri! What was that about?
What's wrong with this picture?
It's like... like...
This is what
adolescence is all about.
There's only one way left, Raharu.
I guess I have to go bust in.
Right.
Our goals might be different,
but the target is the same.
Medical Mechanica.
Mori
Goro
(14)
Shock!
Did something
happen to Hidomi!!!
I dunno. It's because Ide jumped
ahead of us and did this and that.
Bow! Bow wow!
Hibajiri Hinae
Shock!
Did something
happen to Hidomi!
I was worried since she didn't
wake up for hours after the beach.
But she woke up perky and happy.
You know, I think she felt my love.
I finally feel like
I'm her mother now.
Hey, there's a chopper!
The world's upside down!
I'm mad! Those
crappy headphones!
It's an emergency measure
Medical Mechanica prepared.
The personality change
is likely a side effect.
Oh, the Iron.
That's the world smoother!
I think she's cute...
That's... not Hibajiri.
Good morning!
Here's Hidomi-chan!
I'm Hidomi! Hidomi, that is!
She's so cute.
Tee hee hee. Tee hee hee.
Tee hee hee. Tee hee hee!
Please do something,
Miss Haruko!
It's because you didn't
take off her headphones!
I'm sorry about that.
We don't have time to waste.
You know what you need to do.
You like dressing like that.
Medical Mechanica...
We can remove it there.
And you and I chase after him.
We have no other options.
I hope I'm not late to work.
Owww...
Hibajiri-san! What are you doing?
Done!
Wow.
In a single word... This is a song.
A song?
That's right!
There's no oxygen in space.
But the stars spin
around and sing together!
The musical score of the stars...
Oh, I have to go to work.
There's a new ride coming soon!
Wow!
Oh, it's time.
Can I have my payment?
Oh yeah. Here.
Thank you for
your business. Here.
I bought this?
That's right. See you next time.
What's that?
A Viking ship?
How lame! Let's go home.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh. I'm glad you made it.
Tonkichi-san, what's this?
Oh, this is the new main attraction.
What do you mean you
can't find it? You ain't a kid.
I looked everywhere!
But it's nowhere to be found!
How do you lose a big
thing like a flower pot?
Can't you make it again?
It's a one-of-a-kind thing
made from this guy's parts.
There's no way we can make it
from scratch with our technology.
Aw, geez. Oh, have you seen
the carved bear that was here?
You...
No no no, the important
thing is the flower pot.
That was meant for monitoring...
I'm home.
Yeah. We want
to reverse the current of N.O.
If we hypothesize it's a power that
can pull objects from somewhere...
I see. So we should be
able to reverse the direction.
That's right. And...
One, two! Shoot, shoot!
Now reverse the flow!
What are you doing?
Hey, Aiko. Welcome home.
Oh! You're a phenomenon!
You have a fine fist.
You brought
the champion guy again?
Do you want to take
the world with me?
It's like a shooting star.
There's gossip of a weirdo
from the slums is coming here.
I'm sorry.
Your champion dad
has done no wrong, girl...
Champion...
I'll give you this, so forgive us?
You always give me comp tickets,
but where do you get them from?
Well...
That's...
I'd prefer tickets to a beach resort.
The amusement park got a new
ride, but it was a lame Viking.
The Viking ship was installed?
Was it really the Viking ship?
Y-Yeah.
Hey, it's finally...
Yeah. This will be an issue...
What's that about?
Hey, Aiko. Do you know what
happened to the carved bear...
Thanks for taking
part in the test run.
No problem. It's part of my job.
I like that about you.
Plus, I get a bonus right?
That's right. Why?
Huh? Oh...
I wanted to buy a gift.
Dream. Dream. Why do we dream?
Is it because it's named dream?
Whether sleeping or waking
dreams, I have a dream!
I dreamt that I woke up!
Let's go.
Listen. Those headphones
are deep in Hidomi's head...
Operation!!
Get Hidomi Back to Normal
...and are impossible to remove.
She's acting funny...
...since they're receiving
bizarre signals from the plant.
Bizarre signals!
To return her to normal, we need
to cut off these bizarre signals.
Here's the plan.
We'll split into two groups...
...and attack the plant
from inside and out.
Raharu, you destroy
the outer antenna.
Sure, sure.
I'll sneak in with Hidomi...
...destroy the facility inside,
and unlock the headphones.
Hey, that's my job!
I'm not leaving her alone with you.
W-What about me?
Hibajiri!
Yes! I am Hidomi-chan!
Here we go.
That's what I like about you...
We're going in.
From where?
You know the way.
No, I don't.
No plan? You're full of it!
We have to figure it out
either way, so do something!
Shut up! Don't order me around!
They're no use...
What's this treasure?
Oh. That's Mori's girlfriend's...
Don't touch it.
She said it had a high price tag.
High?
So high!
What are you doing!?
Ow...
Why won't you get it?
He... He doesn't want...
What did you do, Ide?
Idiots only do stupid things.
Even though it's
evidence, it's a bit sad.
Yeah. Our research made
a lot of progress because of him.
Well, the shell that remains of him.
Mikan
The owner of this shell isn't
a living creature in our sense.
It's much bigger. Like a being
between living things and planets.
Planets, huh.
That's why its cycle
is years long and...
What's up?
The flower pot.
You lost it.
It's moving.
It only activates
by reacting to N.O.
That means the N.O...
Got a hold of the flower pot...
It's in reverse-flow phenomenon!
Huh?
They went inside your head!
Like a vacuum cleaner!
Hibajiri... What happened to you?
Are you going to stay
like this forever?
I've always been like this.
Always?
I've always honestly...
Shut up already!
Why won't you understand?
He doesn't want that.
What do you know about him?
I do know.
Say that again and I'll kill you.
You need to let him go. Those
who tie him down are my enemy.
Medical Mechanica.
You.
He just...
Shut up and stop talking
about him!
I get what I want.
I'm the one who'll
make him turn around!
You won't be able to.
I understand all of it.
About him, about you.
How dare you.
I'll say it as many times as
you want! Join me, Raharu!
You're me!
Fine...
Raharu, you finally understand!
With you, I know we can...
I'm going to eat you.
Owww...
Hibajiri? Hey, Hibajiri!
Hibajiri!
H-Hibajiri! C-Careful!
I can see everything.
Where is he? My father?
Oh yeah, you don't have a dad.
I don't have a mom either.
But...
Mommy has been waiting.
But he won't come home!
Hibajiri...
If everything's destroyed,
we can start over.
What?
Then Mom wouldn't be crushed,
and Dad wouldn't leave.
If today was an ordinary day like
yesterday, it would've been nice.
Hibajiri! Whoa!
That was close.
I don't need anything special.
The anger, the sadness,
the sobbing and crying.
I don't want to hear it anymore.
That's why this is perfect.
Quit it, Raharu!
Hibajiri... Whoa!
What's going on?
Hibajiri!
Hibajiri! Hang on, Hibajiri!
The headphones...
Ide-kun...
Hibajiri! Are you back to normal?
No, Ide-kun...
Hey...
I'm going to... overflow.
I'm going to overflow.
Overflow...
What are you talking about?
Hibajiri!
No...
I'm going to overflow.
I'm going to...
No!
No... The world is
turning inside out.
What? What's going on?
Hibajiri!
H-Hey, is that the Pirate Ki...
No! But that power is...
It's begun!
H-Hibajiri-san!
What now?
What's going on?
Rolling?
W-W-Wait...
H-Hibajiri!
Quit it, Raharu!
Shut up! Your sunglasses are lame!
How dare you!
Hibajiri!
Dammit!
Ide-kun?
Hibajiri! You woke up...
Ide-kun!
Hibajiri!
Dammit!
Quit it, Raharu!
Hibajiri!
Ide-kun!
C'mon!
S-Sorry! I mean,
I shouldn't be sorry...
Whoa!
Hidomi!
Jinyu!
Don't be looking away!
Stop, Raharu!
Shut up, lame glasses!
Jinyu!
Stop! Raharu!
Jinyu-san! I-It's falling over!
Jinyu!
Stop!!
The plant...
...stood up.
Jinyu...
R-Raharu...
I just want him...
...to be free.
I love him.
That's why I want him
to be free from me.
You don't get it.
Everything belongs
to him from the start.
Contraints. And freedom.
There's nothing in this world
that doesn't belong to him.
That's that.
You're not me.
I see.
Perhaps you're right.
Come with me, Jinyu.
C'mon. Come with me too, Hidomi.
Hibajiri!
I finally understand...
...what you want to do.
So...
...I won't go with you.
So it finally stood up.
It's getting foggy.
It'll go away once the sun's high.
You didn't have
to come, you know.
Or were you scared
that I'd throw it away?
If this had even a fraction
of the power it used to...
Forget about it. Don't worry.
Somewhere in Oozu City
In Front of the Immigration Center Orbit Elevator
Hey there, champ!
Working hard "for tomorrow"?
I did start saving money.
Ah, that's great. Planning is an
important aspect in life, after all.
Don't worry. You're not
far from the warehouse.
Thanks.
Whoa, it's heavy!
Hey! That thing's rare!
Handle it with care!
Sorry!
No worries. It's junk.
Really? Do you know how much...
I totes understand.
I had a hard time throwing away
the first cell phone I got, too.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Come on, let's go!
I'm not into amusement parks.
Go with Marco or something.
He didn't come today.
I think he had work.
- He ditched for a part-time job?
- You're one to talk.
Come on! If we take a girl,
they give you a 99% discount!
I'll invite Aiko-chan, so please?
Well, I didn't really
invite Aiko-chan.
"I want to go to the
amusement park with you...
...but I'm embarrassed to ask."
She was saying stuff like that,
wanting to go. Hey, you listening?
So today I have an important
announcement to make.
I'm going to get married!
So that's why I decided
to quit being a teacher today...
...and I'm going to be
a normal housewife!
Since it's goodbye,
can you hear me out?
About how me and my hubby met?
Yes, let's hear it!
So my hubby and I met at Oozu
Amusement Park around sunset.
A roller coaster was
about to hit clumsy old me...
...when someone
saved me. Yes, him!
Woot woot!
Young ones!
Amusement parks are paradise!
Youngsters, throw away your books!
Go to the amusement park!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Hibaji...
What's wrong? You look down.
Is it girl problems?
I wanted you to be at
the amusement park the most.
I'm not going.
Hibaji!
Please stop, Miss Haruko.
I'd like a word.
Hibajiri, you stay here.
Don't get involved
with Hidomi anymore!
Wow, that line is so cool.
Fine. Let's do this.
You really have no talent.
Nope, nope, nope, nope!
You gotta fight with your own bat.
If you have something you
want to do, you need strength.
Use your hips. Keep your arms intact.
Tuck your chin and tuck your chin.
Nope. You're not good at all!
I don't see any growth.
It's unfortunate. Truly unfortunate.
Stay away from Hidomi!
If being able to take hits counted
as strength, you'd be a big deal.
I thought you'd be better.
That's why I taught
you all those things.
But...
I guess it was all useless.
You know nothing.
You also know
nothing, Miss Haruko.
You haven't been
good at all either!
W-What...
Uh-oh. It may not
make it this time around.
I'll be waiting.
Right now it's 99% off for couples!
Super cheap!
Jeez...
Welcome to
Oozu Amusement Park
Aiko-chan!
You're always like that, Wataru-kun.
You don't understand my feelings!
Misaki...
You know it's true!
I love you.
I love you too!
Yuya!
I want you... I want you
to ride the teacups with me!
Yuya! Why do you always show up?
Wataru, I finally
realized my true feelings.
I don't want to hear it now!
Yuya!
Wataru!
Stop it, boys! Don't fight over me!
How much longer do
I have to stay here?
You just have to stay
right there. Right there.
Young Couples' Day
Pirate Ship Attack
Oozu Amusement Park Attractions
Talk with Dodo-kun!!
Hold it. Not that one.
I thought it was Dodo-kun.
Don't forget we're dealing
with top secret stuff!
Go through the secret
communication mode.
Push the Kiwi-chan strap
in the shopping section.
Which one?
The fluffy one at
the bottom, in the middle.
Forest Nest
Spaghetti
Hey, the link went to the wrong place.
Push "Shisochii's
Chicken Wings" next.
Shisochii's
Chicken Wings
Icarus Fall
"Icarus Fall is the world's
third-fastest falling ride..."
Falling
Penguin Game
Whoa whoa whoa!
Right there. Go back.
That one. The falling one.
Icarus Fall
There are a lot...
The one with Emu-tan.
What? Which one?
With the fluffy wings...
Use words!
There!
Hi there! It's Dodo-kun here!
It's me.
Ah, sorry. Kids get in
a lot of times by mistake.
Dodo-kun!
Hi there!
I saw the Viking ship went in.
There are also Immigration
Control Center matters.
I don't want you to rush this.
What about the flower pot?
Is it complete?
Yeah. It can be activated anytime.
Really?
The plant is up.
What intel do you have?
It's Dodo-kun here! Dodododo!
Go away!
Yeah, you're creepy!
Focus on your job. I sent the data.
This is my job too! Do you know
how much the revenue here...
Can you do it
without the flower pot?
Nope.
If you can't activate that,
a plan won't help.
Shut up. I know that.
Aiko.
What is it?
I'm all dried up.
W-Water...
I don't want to remember
what happened this morning.
Oh my! Hidomi-chan, look!
It must be Jinyu-san. She must've
felt bad about breaking so many.
I guess so.
Hidomi-chan, you've changed.
I'm just back to my usual self.
No. You're different. Completely.
I changed?
I see.
What are you doing?
Have fun at school, Hidomi-chan.
By the way, your friend Ide-kun...
He's very cute.
Why?
I know everything about you.
I'm your mommy after all.
That's not it...
You like him?
That's not what I'm talking about!
You're closing the cafe?
Why? Why would you?
I thought you're going to wait
for Dad to come home here!
I think it's time to stop.
Hi there! I'm Dodo!
Looks like you're all having fun.
Hey, guys!
Kids not even at the end of puberty
have no use other than this, right?
Fire! I mean...
Fire!
They started!
What? What?
Captain! We won't
be able to make it!
Even if we can't, we've got to do it!
Show them!
Even wrinkles that will get
flattened out will fight to the end!
Start the attack!
Immigration Center: Lost and Found Satellite Storage
Oh, look here. Oh my.
What an adorable guest.
You were hungry, weren't you?
You poor thing.
They're doing it?
Woot! You look stylin', Hibaji!
Pretty awesome!
Whoa, hold it! Hold it!
What did I do?
I just a li'l nudge to
the dreams of you youngsters!
Right?
Give him back! Give Ide-kun back!
Whoa! So this is the real strength
of a middle-school student?
You're just like them in the end!
You like that weird bird,
right? How stupid.
You're just a girl in love!
It's Atomsk.
Go!
It's not working!
Dammit!
W-What's going on?
It's here!
Here, here, here! Finally here!
Aren't you satisfied now?
That... That's your dream, right?
It's getting fulfilled.
So can't you let us go?
Give Ide-kun back.
Were you listening
to anything I taught in class?
Give it back.
I want it!
I want to get it back!
To make it mine!
Give it! More!
Are you a crybaby?
You think you can get it just by asking?
Will stomping and crying on the
floor make someone drop it for you?
Then what should I do?
Hand it over.
If you want something you
don't have, hand over what you do.
Then it'll even out.
You're making a deal?
It's not something a teacher should do.
This is the last thing I'll teach you.
Give your power to me.
Is that the correct answer?
You make your own answer.
I learned, Miss Haruko.
I'll stop acting childish.
So that's why...
...I'll take it from you.
Gold star!
Good job! Gimme more!
More!
Hurry! We need to evacuate!
Hit, hit, hit!
Come on, over here!
Thank you, Hibaji!
The time's finally come.
Come over here, Atomsk!
Huh? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
It's huge!
Shoot, this ain't good...
H-Help!
This is bad!
We need to run, Captain!
We can't do that!
Men, gather! Lean forward!
You young'uns are
the energy of space!
I won't ever back down!
Captain!
Hey, you okay?
The champ...
The champ's destructive punch...
He's not...
Aiko...
You came home to me?
But... it's a bit too late now.
Medical Mechanica plans to
capture that monster with this mochi...
...but I don't think it's possible.
And the flower pot is missing.
Aiko. You were the last hope.
That's why, before I knew it,
I was hesitant to use you.
Take this and run.
I don't want it.
Take it!
You planned to use this to buy it, right?
To buy yourself! Freedom!
Why don't you take it.
It's fight money. The ten-count
gong has already been struck.
Aiko, you're free!
What should I do?
The flower pot. A trigger.
Mori
Agh, that was the worst.
Huh? Where's my bat?
What's wrong? You were fine before.
Canti?
Sheesh.
Hey, is this a date?
Fine, call it one!
Woohoo! The flower pot, right?
It's probably at Ide's house.
Did it eat something weird?
Oh no...
Mori-kun?
Hibajiri's mom?
Oh, girlfriend?
Yes...
No, I'm not.
Hey, Ide, you're not
home, right? I'm coming in!
What do you need from Ide?
Hidomi-chan hasn't come home.
I thought she'd be here.
Why here?
I thought they were together.
Why does Ide get all the luck?
That was fast.
Oh my, what's wrong?
Aiko-chan?
A-Aiko-chan?
Oh my...
Are you okay? What's happening?
Mommy?
No way... Hidomi-chan?
Hidomi-chan?
Are you okay? You're not hurt?
I was so worried!
Why?
You don't care about me anymore.
You're closing the cafe, right?
You don't care about
Daddy anymore either.
That cafe was something he left in
my care when he left for the plant.
So were those things on your ears.
Sorry to say it, but it's not here.
That's a prob.
Actually, maybe...
...he came to get it back.
You know, I thought if
I lived at that cafe with you...
...I could wait for him forever.
If I lived an unchanging daily
life there, when he came back...
...I would finally be able
to become a real "mother" to you.
Until then, I wanted
to work hard as your "mommy."
I'm sensitive, even if I don't look it.
If you're looking for
your bat, there it is.
But I was wrong.
You were bound to keep changing.
You'll fall in love and become an adult.
That's why...
Let's do it again together.
The cafe. Let's run it again.
Not to wait for Dad.
But because that's
where my home is.
Because there's something
unchanging there, I can change myself.
Hidomi-chan...
Wait for me, Mom.
Make sure to come
home soon, Hidomi.
And help me run the cafe.
Wait for me.
Miss Haruko.
Did you calm down?
Want some tea?
I'm going to use
this power for myself.
Sounds good. Only kids would
try to act tough and noble.
I'll get out of here
and take Ide-kun back.
That sounds good, too.
But...
not thinking about what happens
next still makes you a kid.
If you take that off, Hibaji,
you won't be able to stay human.
You're all alone.
You think you can still do it?
Oh no...
Y-You're...
Canti!
Pretty awesome.
Then shall we get outta here?
I wonder about that.
A lot was sucked in, after all.
Well, just be careful.
I-I can't pedal anymore!
Huh?
Is this place okay?
What an odd child.
She's just unique!
I-Is that part of her uniqueness?
Y-Yeah.
Outta my way!
There it is!
Make it in time!
In movies you're supposed
to barely make it in time!
There's another one!
Canti!
What the... Where'd it go?
Atomsk.
Ide-kun!
Come out, Atomsk!
Come out, Ide-kun!
I see. Take it, eh?
That's right. If you
want it, just take it!
Eat this!
Jeez, Hibaji! Don't be a third wheel!
Damn it!
No way...
What's going on?
Whoa whoa whoa...
Ide-kun!
Hey! Better not run away.
You became mine!
Didn't you, Atomsk?
Why? Why? Why?
I've been chasing
after you for so long.
Why won't you become mine?
You're mine!
You're mine! You're mine!
You're...
Why...
Can't you see that my body
is filled up with you?
As a kid...
...did you try and fail to draw a picture
of seeing fireworks with your family?
Ide-kun!
You try to draw
countless specks of light...
...but the only way to fill in the
night sky is with black color pencil.
They were lighting up the sky.
They were so colorful and beautiful.
All beautiful things disappear.
I thought this time for sure...
An all-out attack didn't work, eh?
You can go home now!
Um, so what was this
all about in the end?
There was no meaning.
That probably didn't come
for a specific reason either.
Ow.
You're so stupid!
What'll you do now?
Go after it again.
You don't give up.
I'm an adult after all.
You chase it since
you can't catch it.
Want to touch it
since you can't reach it.
Exactly.
Miss Haruko.
Well, you did this and
that to me many times...
...and I appreciate your feelings.
But I just... I just can't...
reciprocate those feelings!
I'm sorry!
Miss Haruko.
Man, you injured me.
That's why I'm going.
Do as you wish. I'll do the same.
Huh? What happened?
It's been a while.
Oh! Chief!
My, your features around your
eyebrows look just like your father's.
Don't! Don't look!
There's nothing I want to be.
There's nothing I want to do.
There's not a way I should be.
But...
What's there is probably...