I'm leaving!
See you later!
Every day is drifting
in an orange light.
To eyes swollen from crying,
a familiar view is somehow novel.
Even if tomorrow is
a gathering of yesterdays...
...though tangled and cracked...
...wearing my favorite
nail art and worn-out loafers...
...I will... in this city...
Pets!
Morning!
Morning, Kana-bun.
What's up? Fight with your dad again?
Well, he sucks the yolk of his
sunny-side up egg right off the plate!
That's gross.
C'mon!
It's not happening, Mossan.
Put down your Dr. P. and fugashi.
Thanks. Want some fugashi?
No thanks. It's too early.
You burn off whatever you eat in the morning.
It's like zero calories!
That doesn't make them zero.
Hey, look at this.
Special Tsuganei Hot Girls Catalog
Tsuganei Hot Girls Catalog?
Look down below.
Tsuganei Beauty
Hijiri
It's Hijiri!
Oh, she's working it.
Wasn't she on something else before?
That was an ad for the mall.
Yeah, that one! She's amazing.
At this rate, Tsuganei will finally...
...have a supermodel?
There's the celebrity!
Shh! The paparazzi might find me.
I'm all tingly! I'm star-struck!
But this magazine's
run is only 50 copies...
Don't be jealous now.
- Shoot! We're late!
- Mossan, run!
W-Wait!
Yikes, Kana tripped!
We'll do something important
for this class after school!
You know, right?
What?
I haven't heard.
Aida!
Yes, sir!
Today's the qualifiers for
the boys' basketball team!
Will we break our
record of 62 straight losses?
Today is the fateful day!
We will be tested!
He's awfully pumped up, but isn't
Sasaki just the team manager?
Uh, yeah. I guess so.
You guess so? You know.
Huh? What are you saying?
Stop teasing her.
Poor Kana.
D-Don't pity me! It's not like that!
Koumoto!
Sorry!
Don't do it again!
What's Sudo's problem?
He's louder than any of us.
- He's such a drag.
- He's too gung-ho.
But he's such a wimp too.
Oh, by the way, wasn't
Sudo saying something?
You mean future plans?
Future plans, huh?
What teenager knows
what their career path will be?
What happened in
their 17 years of life?
You're an average
student and not athletic.
That's the hardest thing to do
according to Ping-Pong Club!
I want to be a pro baseball player's wife.
Or an apparel company CEO's second wife.
Are you Saeko?
I am Saeko.
I wish a talking cat would appear
and give me a magic wand.
Are you gonna watch
the basketball team today?
Guess so. I've got time.
Shall we cheer them on?
Watching these games
can get pretty exciting.
Yep!
Bye!
What are you up to?
See you tomorrow.
See you at Commu-Center after work!
Okay!
It's ready!
Okay.
Thanks for waiting.
Here's your full-moon soba.
Thanks.
O-Oh no! I'll get a new one...
This is fine.
But it looks like Mars
instead of a full moon...
He ate it?!
W-What were you thinking?
Oh boy...
What's a grown man doing?
Got it.
Thanks.
S-Sure.
Air pollution and global warming!
Income disparity and adultery!
This planet is filthier than filthy!
Civilians Space Travel to be Prohibited
Prime Minister Broadcast
So this government, by prohibiting
civilians from traveling into space...
...shall protect this Earth!
Prime Minister!
Ban space travel, huh?
Hey.
- Ban or not...
- Welcome.
...we can't easily go out to space.
But lots of rockets go up lately...
Those are just for the rich and powerful.
They only care about themselves.
Excuse me! Can I get ponshu?
Make it lukewarm.
Between body temp and cold sake,
perfectly balancing taste and aroma...
Sure.
Um, is there
something else you need?
Are you 17?
Um, yes.
But you seem kind of tangled.
Muddled.
Maybe you think every day
will be the same forever?
Seventeen won't wait for you.
Another order!
Uh, right!
Community Center
Got it! Mossan,
looks like you're done for.
No, I'm not giving up yet!
Awaken, my seventh senses!
All right! It's Mossan's
turn to throw out the trash!
Dammit...
I can't believe I lost!
- I'm spent.
- So weird...
I felt the cosmos helping me...
What's wrong, Kana? You look out of it.
Well, a pink-haired woman
came to the soba shop.
She told me, "Seventeen
won't wait for you."
Pink hair? Was she
saying to enjoy youth?
Maybe? Am I tangled?
She's right. You're all tangled.
Especially your earphone cords.
What? They always
get tangled. It's so annoying!
So annoying.
Wait. What's annoying?
Hey! Don't laugh.
You guys are making fun
of me too much lately.
C'mon, Pets!
Sorry. By the way,
what are you doing, Mossan?
Huh? I'm cleaning.
What's that?
You know. Where it
goes shooting in the air?
Bottle rockets?
Yeah, that!
I have this urge
to build something.
Can I try?
-Lemme see. Gimme. Lemme touch.
- What's this?
-Are these the wings?
-Yeah.
- This'll probably have too much drag.
Design over function!
Hey, what's this?
Weights!
This?
No! That's a bike valve!
A rocket on a bike?
Yeah.
You don't know what a bike valve is?
Yeah, never touched one before.
Shut up and listen!
You don't have enough bottles.
There's another case.
Leave the drinking to me.
Okay.
We'll work together
to complete this rocket!
Yeah.
Such low energy!
That's right.
Right there. Take that
and shove it. Twist it.
Birdwatching? This late at night?
Why are you in this town?
Or should I say this planet?
Everything in order, sir!
Are you searching for it again?
The NO...
Wow, you go straight there.
No matter what you do,
they're not going to stop.
You know that already...
You're no fun, as usual.
You don't know until you try.
Yikes. Wow, it's so big...
Do you think it'll fly? It will, right?
Let's send it off! Right now!
No, it's not ready yet.
You didn't drink enough Pepper?
Diabetes won't wait.
That's not it!
Then what?
It's plain!
You're right!
I'm leaving!
What about breakfast?
Civilian Space Travel Restrictions Enacted
I'm not hungry today.
Bunta!
That'll gross girls out.
Make this part red and...
...this part yellow! And this pink!
Pink! Hot pink!
Mossan, you're good at drawing.
How about sequins here?
I like it!
Let's shop before
going to Commu-Center.
I had a date, but I'm flaking.
I'll take off work too!
All right!
Let's do it!
Any of you go shopping here?
Nope.
They're so stuck up.
Me neither! The shopping district's
losing customers because of this.
T-This is beyond
what I imagined...
- Like a pro!
- This is sick!
- Remarkable! It's so cute!
- "Remarkable"?
Okay! Let's make it fly!
Outer space... here we come!
Ow...
Is everyone okay?
W-What is this?
A pin?
It's been destroyed...
Catastrophically.
W-What now?
Ew, gross!
Let's get out of here!
Hey! Kana!
Why are you crying?
Huh? Why?
Kana-bun! Let's go!
Hey. It's pink hair.
Ow...
Sorry! Did she die?
It's so hard!
Kana-bun! Kana-bun!
Wake up, Kana-bun!
You wanna die here?
Here, drink this!
This too!
I have something too!
She came back to life!
All right!
I'm so glad...
Ow!
Ow...
What? What is this?
What's this?
A flower?
Dammit...
Gross.
It's like a kaiju movie...
But this is real, right?
That was a surprise.
Didn't think it'd enlarge.
You were at the soba shop...
I'm Haruko Haruhara.
A space investigator for
the Space Police Brotherhood!
B-Bro...
Space?
She said it twice.
Anyway...
In order to beat
that thing up, I want that.
"That" what?
Don't mind me.
I won't hurt you.
Stop struggling...
Oh! It's almost out!
There!
T-This is...
...a 1967 model Mustang!
All right!
Dammit! Don't get cocky
just 'cause you got bigger!
That's why it's
the fragile teen years.
If it broke, just make it again.
She's right.
Target neutralized.
N.O. is the ability to open via the
thought difference of left and right brain...
...hyper-spatial channels
to attract objects.
What are you trying to do
here on Earth, Raharu?
It's the ocean! The wind's salty!
Whoa, the water's cold!
Are you ready?
Okay!
Countdown from five...
Four, three, two, one...
Blast off!
It's flying!
W-Wait...
It's heading this way!
Kana, you look like a ghost!
It's October!
I'm taking you down with me!
H-Hold on...
Wait! I'm not ready for this...
Kana-bun...
Let's negotiate. Let's talk...
It's so cold!
If I catch a cold, it's your fault!
The shimmering ocean
burns into our memories...
...as the day ends
with us unable to fly.
But this doesn't last forever.
You don't know what's
truly important until it breaks.
I think that's probably
when I realized it.
Not just me, but I'm
sure everyone else, too.
The album was fifth
on the Billboards last year.
And my mentor shot
the cover. It freaked me out.
That's cool.
Oh yeah.
Can you model next time?
Model?
You can invite your
friends too if you want.
Sounds fun.
Right?
I want to start thinking about
making a photo book, you know?
I can't be a college student forever.
You're right.
Oh yeah.
A senior at my college started
a company. He asked me...
So Bunta didn't eat them
again today. Mom was so mad.
Some people don't like them.
I do.
Right? People hate
them without trying them.
In fact, tomatoes are the
world's tastiest vegetable!
Depends on the person.
You think so?
Is that Hijiri?
They kissed!
Did you see? They just kissed!
Yeah, I guess.
They smooched! Smooch!
Calm down.
My head hurts.
I didn't get enough sleep.
I thought you didn't want a boyfriend.
I said not any boy in class.
Harsh!
What does he do?
He's in college.
You attract all sorts of guys.
Yeah, I know.
Yajima!
Y-You're really dating
a college student?
That came from nowhere.
It's out.
Word gets around fast.
It happens.
I-Is it true? It is?
Go, Sasaki!
Give Hijiri Yajima back!
Give Back Yajima
Give her back!
Dating college students is improper!
Give back? She wasn't
yours in the first place.
Can you make them stop?
They're noisy, and it's out of hand.
It's not my problem.
What's with you?
You're the cause.
Let's calm down!
Enough! It shouldn't
matter who Hijiri dates!
What, Koumoto?
Give Back Yajima
Don't butt in just because Sasaki is with us!
H-He has nothing to do with it!
Yeah! I don't!
We don't need a romcom plot.
No! I'm not interested in him!
You could humor them, you know.
I can't humor immature guys.
Ooh, burn!
Not just the guys, but the girls.
Does it matter?
We're graduating.
That's true...
Is that new? He bought it for you?
That's right.
That brand's worth a used car.
Wow!
Hey, why are you using my stuff?
Why not?
I want to try grown-up makeup.
That bad?
You're too young for this.
Really?
I guess so.
Oh yeah. Did you all want
to come with me this weekend?
I'm Toshio Shioya. Nice to meet you.
Thanks.
Um...
Pho... Pho... Photo photo?
Tsuganei Village
Photographer.
I'm in college, but you could say I'm a pro.
Shall we start?
C'mon.
Here we go!
Okay!
I see. Good, good.
Let's keep going.
How about we go there and
do something more ennui.
Hey, aren't there a lot of dogs?
Kebab
Strays? I've never seen a toy poodle.
I hope they don't have rabies.
Kebab
Oh, Haruko-san?
Hey, Kana-bun!
Why a kebab vendor?
Meat! Meat!
Budget reasons? Forced labor?
Meat!
This is a business.
I don't want poor students here.
Four orders for them.
He's so grown-up.
Thanks!
Here you go.
Yay!
Oh, tomatoes! Look!
Yeah yeah.
Looks delicious.
Whew, it's hot.
Toshio.
Toshio?
Oh, sorry.
Um, may I take a photo of you, miss?
I dunno. I don't have
makeup on right now.
Just one shot?
You can keep the change.
Nope, go through my agent.
I'll keep the change though.
C'mon. Please?
C'mon, let's go. It'll get cold.
She's got skills.
They left us behind.
Hijiri's amazing! She's sparkling!
It's hot! What is this?
This is so spicy! Really spicy!
It's a little spicy, but...
It's perfectly spicy.
Really!? Really really?
Special space mustard.
It might've been too grown-up for Kana-bun.
Grown-up...
For reals?
Yeah, it's really really?
No way.
Really.
Here you go!
Here.
Okay.
The soup spilled though.
Don't worry. It's the usual guy.
Mr. Full Moon...
Regarding the artificial island
on Tsuganei City Bay...
Sorry for the wait. One full-moon soba.
I'm tired of waiting.
Again?
Yes... again.
You're not coughing!
I've matured.
Artificial Island Rocket Base Expansion
Prime Minister Broadcast
I hear there are voices of opposition.
We the government,
as dignified grown-ups...
...ask that everyone act
as sensible grown-ups on this matter.
What does grown-ups mean?
Like eating soba alone
on a Sunday evening...
Catch!
Thanks.
I knew it was spicy.
Will both of you go shower already?
Bunta, you can go first.
What? I'm watching TV.
If you two don't go,
Dad can't take his bath.
Rocket Base Construction Forced Through
Just five more minutes.
Hey, Bunta, got a girlfriend?
Huh? Yeah.
No way.
Even though you can't eat tomatoes?
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah, sorry.
I thought I should tell you in person.
Since we're grown-ups.
Yeah.
It's not you. So don't feel bad.
I'm fine. It doesn't bother me.
I thought so. Good.
Yeah.
See ya. Thanks for everything.
Sure. Bye.
Cute earrings!
Right?
She came with a college dude!
Quit it!
Hijiri!
Show us the pictures
from the other day!
The ones your boyfriend took.
You got the files, right?
Oh.
Do we look like models?
Maybe.
You look thinner in photos, right?
I thought it's the opposite.
But he's a pro. He'd use great angles!
I'm stoked!
- I've been thinking about Toshi.
I want to see him soon.
- Can I have my necklace back?
You're not using it, right?
Yajima-san!
Yes?
Your friends ordered drinks.
Okay.
I don't care if I get broken...
I don't care if I throw it all away...
Love is precious.
I'll leave it here.
C'mon, Hijiri!
We can hear you outside.
Tone it down a bit.
But we lost our Commu-Center.
Thanks to those giant pins.
There's nowhere else.
I know, but...
Thank you!
Yay!
Only 35 points!
Hijiri's next!
No thanks, I'm working.
You can sing one song.
No thanks.
Which song?
No thanks!
But you need to sing...
I said no!
I'm just joking.
Jeez! You scared me!
Sorry.
Ah...
Put in my song! My favorite!
Let's dance, girls!
Yeah!
Hijiri was acting kinda strange.
Really? She seemed normal.
She's always kinda aloof.
Wasn't she being too cheerful?
You're overthinking it, Mossan.
LOL
You think so?
Yeah.
I'm off for the day.
What should I do? What should I do?
What should I do?
Know how many confessed
to Hijiri in middle school?
Like 30?
No, more than 50.
108 guys.
Whoa.
Annoying number.
She rejected most.
I wouldn't expect less from Hijiri.
She had a different aura about her.
It's midnight.
He said he's coming, right?
Yeah, when I texted earlier.
Maybe we shouldn't do this.
He's here!
Oh. Where's Hijiri?
Huh?
Did you bring it for her?
Huh? Um...
Hijiri told me to meet her here.
She's giving the necklace back, right?
Necklace? I don't know
what he's talking about.
W-We don't understand you!
I think Hijiri arranged
to meet him here too.
Hijiri!
Why are you all here?
Toshi! Did you get
my necklace already?
D-Don't look, Hijiri!
Close your eyes!
I didn't think it would be Haruko-san.
He dumped me.
He said he likes someone else.
Well, it happens.
Right?
No, it's not right.
Why are you so calm about this?
You'll understand
soon enough, Kana.
I won't understand.
No way.
I don't even want to understand!
Kana-bun!
But Hijiri looked so happy.
You seemed more adult than usual...
Oh shoot. Whoa...
So I couldn't let this pass.
I just couldn't and...
I don't know...
Well, this is our problem.
It doesn't concern you, so stay quiet.
I know it doesn't concern me...
But...
...she's my friend.
Kana...
H-Hey, Kana.
Um, it's getting big...
Yes, it is a big deal!
Two people who liked each
other are breaking up!
No, that's not what we mean...
Huh?
Welcome!
Oh, Kana-bun...
Hey, that's mine!
Got a driver's license?
Not yet...
Then I'll lend you mine.
W-What? I can't drive yet!
Guys have charm, girls have guts,
and Nasser's the president of the UAE.
Right!
Ow...
This is amazing! Just amazing!
This will get me... the Pulitzer!
Dammit...
Huh? Wha?
Dammit!
Aren't they getting closer?
Watch out!
Where is it? Where is my camera?
What? This sucks!
Dammit!
I can't!
Pets, go without me.
Okay.
You gave up on me so quickly!
Hijiri, are you okay?
I might have some
talent with driving!
Good job, Mr. Low-Fuel Consumption.
Go!
Got it!
Michael... Bay!
Turn!
Whew, I'm so tired.
Good job.
Where'd it go? Hey.
Toshio.
Let's go home, Hijiri-chan.
We've gone through a lot.
I think I like you more.
You think she'll take you back?
Scum.
I can't take it anymore!
W-Wait, let's not do this...
Mossan, stop!
Let go, Hijiri.
It's okay! I'm fine!
Why? Let me go!
Because I'm the same!
I'm no better than him...
Acting cooler...
Pretending everything is fine...
Looking down on others
like I'm a grown-up...
It was dumb.
I was dumb.
So...
I'm going to stop it now.
Toshio.
It doesn't look good on me.
Don't compare me to you, all right?
Nothing good happens
from hanging out with kids...
Chance!
So sudden!
Wow, so tiny.
Well, grown-up or kid,
I don't think it matters.
What's important
is how big you are.
Anyway, those are on me!
It's spicy.
Ring... Ring... Ring...
Man, why isn't anyone picking up?
We're unable to answer right now.
Please leave a message
when you hear the "woof."
Gah! Shut up!
We don't have much time left...
Under Construction
Why are you waving
the stick like that?
To keep awake.
It's raining. Why don't you take off?
Have a nice day, sir!
Daruma Moving
See that?
Why me?
This is the worst morning!
Got a dryer, Pets?
I have a towel you can use.
Classic.
Aida! They're showing!
Completely revealed!
Shut up. You strip too!
Me? I don't want to!
Sasaki-kun is so thin.
Maybe Kana should
take a good look.
W-What for?
Dammit! My bag's dead!
Wow, you're like a salesman.
Mossan, we can only bring
300 yen worth of snacks...
That last part will be on
the test! It is on it! Study it!
- Okay.
- Got it.
First Love by Shimazaki Touson
One more thing.
College-plan worksheets.
Koumoto! Yajima! Hetada!
Turn them in this week!
Oh, I completely forgot.
Remember to turn them in
or I'll get in trouble!
Please!
What are you going
to write down?
Koumoto, Yajima, Hetada...
Mossan?
What is all this? It's amazing!
Really? You think so?
I know you're good
at drawing, but clothing design?
I know it doesn't suit me, but...
It's very you, Mossan.
Really? Well, I entered
something like a contest, too.
First Round Cleared
You made the first cut.
You're amazing!
Stop, stop. It's only the first round.
I was just lucky.
You look happy.
You suck at being humble.
Why didn't you tell us
you had career dreams?
Yeah. Only you turned
in the college-plan sheet.
It's hard to tell people
you want to be a designer.
No! We should share
our dreams! We'd support you!
All right...
About the Tsuganei Bay
rocket base being built...
...for use by government VIPs
and the wealthy to escape Earth...
...as some reports state...
Tsuganei City Bay Artificial Island
New Rocket Deployment
Prime Minister Broadcast
It's absolutely groundless.
Completely false!
She lies as if it's breathing.
Is that true?
Way far-fetched!
It's true! He stood by my pillow!
The soba god?
Riding a bowl? Holding chopsticks?
What else?
Hair in soba dreadlocks.
And he quit DJing to sell soba.
He's out of his mind.
Don't mock people's jobs! Eat up!
They'll get mushy!
Okay.
But honestly, I want God
or anything to show up.
I'm really worried.
It feels like this
isn't the time to slurp soba.
You're lucky. You've got modeling.
It doesn't interest me.
That's just people talking.
Pets, you're going to college, right?
It's just me. What do I do?
Just be yourself.
You're the eternal high schooler.
Hey, quit it.
Mossan inspired me to give my all.
You can't.
What? I can, too.
Not just you. I can't either.
Despite the appearance,
Mossan is pretty intense.
Like decorating our
middle-school festival.
How so?
Our school was
a mess senior year...
...and no one wanted
to work on the festival.
Nothing was ready up
till the day before it...
...but Mossan said,
"If we're doing it, let's do it right."
She stayed at school alone,
making arches, signs, and origami flowers.
She made it fancy.
She worked the haunted house
while cooking yakisoba too.
That's crazy...
She's a machine.
She's unbelievable.
See? Unbelievable, right?
Yeah... Her eyes are totally dead.
She's even eating her fingers.
She's working too hard.
It's like her full-time job.
Mossan, maybe you should stop...
Mossan!
Hmm, this is...
Doctor, is it that bad?
Wait, why Haruko-san?
The doctor look works.
A complete exam is needed.
Remove those clothes!
Okay!
No, you girls too.
Huh?
Why do we have to?
- Nice. The parts that stick out do!
What is this?
- What are you looking at?
C'mon, let me observe you and touch you.
You naughty girls!
I like your thin waist.
Your boobs are nice too.
My bust?
But this is definitely the one.
That? That's my weapon?
M-Mossan!
H-Hang on!
Doctor! Her condition is...
Scalpel! Chainsaw!
That electric-shock thingy!
Doctor, will she be fine?
Isn't it presumptuous
for humans to intervene...
...in the life and
death of living creatures?
Gyumaru's limited-run kalbi lunch set...
Ambiya's roll cake...
Sakamoto Shoten's piping-hot
Hokkaido danshaku croquette.
Yubido's strawberry
chocolate dorayaki.
Parakke's thick-cut
800 gram steak, well-done.
Bakery Melcie's pumpkin pie.
Tatsugoyama's
extra-large hokke lunch set...
I can't eat any more...
It's just overwork.
And she ate too much.
She's been working
day and night lately.
I wish we could simply pay
for design school for her...
But our Engel's
coefficient is rather high.
That chicken looks yummy.
Your katsudon looks good, too.
And she hasn't been sleeping
much because of the contest...
Meat fully loaded!
Sis, get up.
It's time for dinner.
Hey! That's bad luck!
She's been working a lot so
she can go to design school...
Yeah.
Mossan never told us
how hard it's been for her.
That's why I said
she's unbelievable.
Hey, I have an idea.
All clear! All clear!
Backing up. Backing up.
Haruko-san again? Why?
I told you this is my part-time
job, too! Maybe I didn't!
Too slow! Faster!
I want you to line
these up artistically.
Pets dear, it's still dirty over here!
I'm exhausted.
No more. I'll die.
But you know...
It kinda feels good to do
something for a friend.
Yeah.
I... guess.
Let's finish this! Swing the baton!
Even the da-da-da thing!
Mossan!
What are you doing?
You shouldn't push yourself!
W-What? That was sudden...
Who told you to do this?
I said who told you to do this?
No one did. Don't butt in.
B-But we're worried you're
keeping stuff to yourself...
That's butting in!
Go home!
I have to fulfill
my dream on my own!
Mossan is so stubborn.
I guess.
She doesn't have to work so hard.
That's true.
It's pointless if she ruins her health.
She might not make the contest.
I'm not saying you aren't right...
Mossan's dream is hers after all.
Maybe it wasn't our place to butt in.
Again?
Huh?
May the Force be with...
I look away and this happens.
No self-control.
You a teenage boy?
I'm sorry.
And you keep drawin'
the losers. Big losers.
Pullin' out Medical Mechanica
robots. You really got no luck.
I'm sorry I'm useless.
If you can't do anythin',
why not become a hikikomori, eh?
I'm really stupid. It's such an
important dream for Mossan.
I dunno.
Plus, it's fine if you
have a dream or don't.
Oh, hold on a sec.
I have call waiting!
Hello? Hello? Helloooo?
Useless! Totally useless dial-up!
You don't have a dream,
so you wanna be helpful, yo.
Is that really for others?
Or is it really for yourself?
Why rap?
Got no dreams, so I
wanna be useful to others.
Isn't that just ego?
Don't have the luck to be useful.
Can't find what matters most.
That kind of night, let's go dancing.
Right, it's time for fighting.
Even though HQ is doing nothing
for me, I beat up robots all alone.
In this never-ending battle.
No communication.
Missing all forms of transmission.
And I'm scared of Internet bashing.
C'mon, freestyle!
Jeez...
Hey, Mossan!
Sorry, no Dr. Pepper.
This soda implying something?
Oh, sorry.
Well, it's like you.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Well, for that too.
But about me butting in...
I said it's fine.
It's not. I didn't really say I'd stop.
I won't just do as I please.
Let me help you right.
Like how?
Not by sewing or going
to work in your place.
More support work.
Like an assistant?
I don't get it.
Real designers
have assistants, right?
So you can practice with me.
The contest is soon!
Let me help you with anything!
I know I'm being pushy...
...but it'll be better
than doing it all yourself!
Pulling the fabric through.
It curves, and I can't sew it right.
Can you help me?
Hey! Can I borrow the sewing kit?
Sure, don't lose any needles!
Okay!
What's she up to?
It seems she's helping
her friend make a dress.
Though she's clumsy like Dad...
Creation Complete
Tournament
Complete creation before the tournament, for tomorrow!
(1) Effectiveness through teamwork!!
How about this one?
It's not quite right...
Faster!
Okay!
Complete creation before the tournament, for tomorrow!
(1) Efficiency through teamwork!!
(2) Raise stamina through basic strength training!!
Increase your speed!
Yes, sir!
Complete creation before the tournament, for tomorrow!
(1) Efficiency through teamwork!!
(2) Raise stamina through basic strength training!!
(3) Make sure you're getting enough vitamins and
nutrients so you can recover from exhaustion.
Creation MUST BE Complete!!
Tournament
Yeah!
24th National Clothing Design Contest
Regional Qualifiers: Results Presentation
Those clothes are so cute!
They're really good.
The models are pretty, too.
Here are the three finalists!
And we will finally announce
the grand-prize winner!
It's almost time...
Yeah.
You're too nervous, Mossan.
Yeah...
Surviving the initial judging...
Who will take the crown?
The next top designer
will be selected right here!
It'll be fine. We all worked hard together.
I know we got it.
The grand-prize winner is...
No. 28, Hana Tondabayashi-san!
Please come up!
Me? Me?
Way to go!
Congratulations!
B-But... you worked hard.
This just wasn't your day.
The cards didn't line up.
It's fine.
No matter how hard you work,
sometimes things don't work out.
It's all about results.
I know that.
But...
But... I had a lot of fun.
I couldn't have done
it without you all.
Mossan...
Please take a look at
the grand-prize design!
What's going on?
Where's the model?
Why isn't the dress coming out?
P-Please wait a moment...
But as a former Space
Collection rep top model...
- ...I can't wear something so bland!
- That's a problem!
- Oh, this one's good.
- That's not the right one!
C'mon! Music!
Yeah!
That's Mossan's...
Why Haruko-san?
I don't know... I don't know, but...
So cool!
Whose design is this?
I-It's mine...
Here. Coco Chanel.
Uh, but...
Mossan! Get up there!
W-What? Can I?
Mitchell   Kokorozashi Seikei   Sekai Teki
Hey, you're a phony model!
What are you doing?
Yikes! A world-class designer!
Celebrity Kick!
Party-people Punch!
It's dangerous here, Mossan!
Let's scram!
Goodbye. Adios. Sayonara.
T-Tell us how you feel right now.
Um, these results are disappointing,
but I'll use this frustration...
...to pursue being a model now!
It figures. Mossan is...
...way unbelievable.
The lines connecting pin to pin...
Within the lines are
the plants of each region...
With the purpose
to flatten everything?
You didn't knock.
Rude, as usual.
I don't know Earth manners.
So what'll you do?
Nothing. I'm just observing.
Figures. You're no fun.
Don't meddle any further.
Medical Mechanica won't stay silent.
All you do is talk.
Well, I'm gonna do it my way.
Buh-bye!
If only these guys were interesting.
First Love by Shimazaki Touson
"A maiden who just tied up her hair,
I saw by the apple orchard."
"The flower comb in her hair..."
What is a flower comb?
Fight!
On!
Sasaki...
Hey, hey, hey, why are
you making that sound?
Tsuga High, fight!
On!
Fight!
Haruko-san?
Hey, Sasa. How do you read this?
Y-You mean "mediator"?
What about this?
"Stockpile"...
"Kuri manjuu"...
And this one?
Oh? What a serious look...
I see it!
The flames of jealousy!
Shut up! Jeez!
Yeah, leave her alone, guys.
P-Pets...
Okay!
Attention! You may be
distracted, but attention!
Basketball Club Substitute Coach
Haruhara Haruko
There's a reason Coach Haruhara is here!
Hey, Aida! Tell them!
I can't! I... I don't
know what to say!
Sasa, please?
Why me?
Who cares who says it?
Can't hide her annoyance.
Can't stop quipping.
Hurry and tell us!
This is gross!
Why me?
The Kita High basketball team
who beat us at regionals...
...had 10 out of 13
students transfer schools...
...so we'll be taking their
place at the next game.
Please come watch us!
You did a great job!
Everyone, clap!
That's a lot of transfers.
We were lucky.
Aida!
Show us something!
You suck!
We came to watch!
Don't give up! Focus!
It's so hot.
We're being steamed.
Oh, that handkerchief is cute.
Wanna trade with this?
Sure. But I made this.
You know... coming to this
hot and sweaty place is tiring.
People usually don't cheer
for the team manager.
Go!
Aida!
Hey, what's the winning
score in basketball?
There's no scoring goal...
That looked painful.
Nice shot, Aida.
What are you doing, Aida?
Shut up! Back at you!
Listen! Fight! Just do it!
Don't lose and you'll win! That's all!
Guys, focus. The number of
shots were down second quarter--
Hey. When is this over?
You should be the one focusing!
T-This is unrelated to the game...
Shut up!
Just shut up and prep
sports drinks for the bench!
Trade this for your chicken?
That's not a fair trade...
Cut it out!
Are they fighting?
Yeah! Go for it!
Sasaki...
You know I want to...
I really want to...
That hurts! Let go!
Ouch!
It backfired!
I-I'm sorry!
I-I'm fine...
Maybe not.
I'm sorry.
Here.
Liger Balm works
best for pain relief.
Rub this on me.
You're good.
I'm team manager...
Wow, vulgar.
Sudo-sensei!
Higher... Towards my groin.
L-Like this...?
Yeah... Right there.
You're touching there, too?
She's raunchy.
That attack has no weakness...
Oh! Sorry!
Sasa! Ecchi, sketch, one touch...
What the heck? So dumb...
Whoa! What's that?
Just kidding.
Sorry, sorry.
So... What are you going to do?
What's there to do?
I-I don't...
...have any feelings...
My head...
You okay?
Here it comes.
Is she throwing in the towel?
Her legs are weak.
I can't deal with this!
She ran off.
Koumoto...
I almost had it.
Hey, Sasaki.
Is he dead?
He had It coming.
What are they doing?
They're not playing seriously.
Yeah. They're so weak.
About the unidentified pins
that appeared all over the world...
There are malicious
hoaxes being spread...
...about alien attacks and...
What's going on?
A-Are you all right, Kana-chan?
If you need the day off...
I'm fine!
Mysterious Giant Pins
Appearing Around the World
Prime Minister Broadcast
The spirit of fraternity is key!
Love is sincere! Love thy neighbor!
Yes! Love will save the world!
Everyone's talking about love!
Sorry! I will take off!
We are analyzing
the pins as we speak.
With our government's
scientific capacity...
Yes, I've been told
I look prettier in person.
I haven't said that.
Look at these bumps.
I'm allergic to soba.
Did you know it can cause death?
Everyone dies eventually...
But there's a difference
between now and later.
Instead of slurping on
bad soba, please do your job.
Due to reduction in staff,
HQ isn't functioning anymore...
So when will that thing move?
Two weeks at the earliest.
I believe it'll start to
actually flatten in a month.
I guess we need
to amend the plans.
Oh, and there were
several sightings of that
Haru-something alien.
I've heard you're
not unfamiliar with it.
It was a long time ago.
I don't care. Just don't
cause any more problems.
You cause too many problems...
Oh? Isn't this going
to cause problems, too?
I'm just checking on your wound.
Just looking?
You should soak more.
I'm all healed, so don't worry.
Then I should check.
Oh? It's hard work
being a bathing officer.
Immigration.
Those who don't know
their manners need punishment...
Hey! What are you doing?
Here you go!
W-What is this?
C'mon, just get it out.
You're gonna touch me there?
There!
What's this?
I knew you were a boring guy.
I hope no one gets hurt again...
Hey, what should I do?
I wouldn't know.
Just push him
down and mount him.
Can you be serious here?
Well...
This is when friends
help each other!
I don't have experience
with this. Give me advice.
Yikes, Sasaki!
Koumoto.
Let's see...
It's cramped...
Go for it, Kana!
W-W-What's up?
Um, uh, thanks for coming today.
It's no big deal...
How did you find us?
I asked classmates.
And when I went to your house,
they said you come to this park a lot.
No, no, no!
Scary, scary, scary!
To her house?
Is he a stalker?
Love is blind.
Were you okay?
The ball hit you...
It wasn't as bad
as getting drop-kicked.
Drop-kicked?
"Don't stray off topic."
Don't worry about it. I'm fine.
Oh, that's good.
Actually, I had something
I wanted to tell you.
Here it comes!
Nothing's going on.
With Haruko-san.
Oh, okay...
As a team manager,
I can't ignore someone in pain...
I-I guess...
Yeah...
And?
W-What now?
Confess! You can do it!
No way, no way, no way!
"Spiritualism"?
Koumoto, you okay?
No mukumuku!
I-I know...
Koumoto?
Koumoto? Does your head hurt?
I-I'm fine...
No, I'm not!
She ran off again.
Koumoto?
Nice job
Jeez! What am I doing?
Whoa! Can you knock first?
Mom says to come eat dinner.
I don't want any.
What? On a diet?
Shut up. Hey, how is it
going with your girlfriend?
Pretty good. She's at
the beach right now.
Look.
See?
Bunta-kun, let's go swimming
That pen is cute.
This?
Trade with me.
Is that a brush pen?
That's original!
Gimme something thicker!
Please. Something thick and stiff.
I think 0.5 mm HB is stiff enough.
What? No, no!
Jeez...
She's troubled.
She's in agony.
This is adolescence.
By the way, why Sasaki?
He's frail. And team manager.
Paroxysmal kinesigenic
choreoathetosis, right?
Yeah, something like that.
What's that?
Sasaki-kun played
basketball in middle school...
...but it seems he has a rare
condition where he can't exercise.
That's why he's team manager?
I shouldn't have judged! Sorry, Sasaki!
I used to be a sickly kid too,
so I understand how he feels.
Have you seen Sasa?
W-We haven't.
If he's not in class, the cafeteria maybe?
Oh, that's true.
Um!
Why are you looking for him?
It doesn't concern you.
T-This could be trouble.
Sparks are flying.
Why doesn't it concern me?
What's up? That's an ugly expression.
I-It's nothing!
Something's up.
Maybe you got your heart broken?
Yikes!
She's riling her up!
Well, you're too immature
for feelings or relationships.
See ya!
Kana-bun, good job!
You held out!
You don't want
to take the first shot.
I've decided.
I made my decision.
What's that?
You don't know Dan Dan Dunk?
It was serialized in Bon Bon.
I don't know what
Dan Dan or Bon Bon means.
Oh? It's a classic...
Y-You okay?
Y-Yeah. It hurts when I move suddenly,
or my heart pitter patters.
Pitter Patte....?
Yeah...
U-Um...
If you're... If you're interested...
Go! Get it out!
A bit more!
Smooch!
Kiss!
Giiirg!
Giiirg?
Huh? Why?
What's wrong?
I'm not feeling the pitter patter.
I don't feel the sparkle.
Ouch...
My butt! My butt!
What is that?
Another robot?
He ate him!
Sasaki was eaten alive!
They merged?
S-Sasaki!
Jeez...
Don't look so smug!
An iron wall...
Gotta watch him.
Sasaki-sun's good at basketball.
Yeah. Though he's mostly robot.
Dammit! Well then...
She retreated!
This is...
The game-making...
...three pointer!
She flew!
The left hand...
...just holds it in place!
It's all about the dunk.
B-ball is great...
Whoa...
Sorry, Sasaki!
I think... I made a mistake.
What do you mean?
The bell rang!
Let's go!
Wait for me!
I think... I'm not ready for this yet.
I'm really sorry! See ya!
In the end, it was
like Haruko-san said.
I'm not ready for love yet...
And I think the real
pitter-patter is...
I hoped every day...
Each and every day...
...would always, always be like this.
That's what I thought.
So cute!
I want one, too.
Ask your mom.
M-Morn--
Good idea. Trade you?
No way! This is my favorite!
Koumoto-san.
Ready, set, go!
This feels so good!
Can I do a front flip next?
Hey, where's Mossan?
A walrus! A walrus appeared!
I'd prefer a manatee!
Really?
Really really?
Is that true?
I read it online.
I saw that.
Earth's going to disappear?
I don't think it's true.
But it's super hot now.
What's going on?
I heard they're
preparing a migration plan.
Unusual Weather Patterns Around the World
We'll get soggy, like soba...
Is the iron linked to this weather?
There are reports
they're appearing worldwide!
Are the rumors true?
Will Earth become extinct?
Uh... well...
There is a deeply rooted reason.
I'm not just saying that.
Unusual Weather Patterns Around the World
Is the Iron-Shaped Building to Blame?
Prime Minister Broadcast
Yes. I don't recall.
I'm different from you.
Only the rich are migrating to Mars!
Don't play dumb!
That was a bad impersonation!
Incoming call from Kitaki
Hey, Kanda!
How dare you let this happen!
Where'd that come from?
It's more like I was embarrassed.
Look at my sweaty pits.
They have pads you can wear.
We're short on cargo vessels and
need to cut migration numbers!
This is on you!
Then I'll resign. Right away.
Who cares about
a low-level official's head!
More importantly, that iron!
What are their reps saying?
There are no reps over there.
That's what we're dealing with.
I swear...
This woman upset them, right?
Well, I won't deny that possibility...
I don't care. Just get it done!
I should have gotten it cold.
It's so hot...
Ceiling Serve!
Whoa, it got carried by the wind!
Good one! Great shot!
Set! Quick!
Here we go!
Back attack!
Pets!
Huh? Where's Pets?
She was there a moment ago.
Maybe she got out?
What's next period?
Math.
What? I'll sleep through it for sure.
Can you turn up the AC?
She's not here.
Maybe she left early.
That's unusual.
Maybe she escaped.
Her family's rich.
Huh? What are you talking about?
You know, migration. To Mars.
Mars?
What are you trying to say, Aida?
I'll rub MUHI on your face!
Did I say something wrong?
Jerk.
Mars? Rich?
Government official?
Yeah, high up the government.
That's why she's wealthy.
Really?
How do you not know?
You knew her since grade school.
She never told me.
I can't believe it.
When did you two find out?
From Yoshie?
The walking gossip column.
Her parents are gossips, too.
Oh, I see...
Head straight home, guys.
Sure thing.
You too, dude.
Yes, ma'am.
You know...
This is kinda strange.
School Closed
Yeah. School just closed.
Well, it is hot...
Nothing we can do about it.
Blast preparations complete!
Five seconds to ignition.
Four... Three... Two...
It's useless.
You said you were just observing.
Don't piss them off anymore.
You're wearing a suit in this heat?
You're the model bureaucrat.
Get your hands off the detonator.
What if I say no?
Well? What if I say no?
Why are you
obsessed with this planet?
No reason. I just don't
want things to be boring.
What are you planning to do?
They can't be stopped...
Till each and every planet in this
universe is flattened for no reason.
Humans resisted, too...
But no matter what weapon we used,
we couldn't dent this plant.
Yeah, probably.
The government will save only the chosen.
The rest will be left behind.
I'm tired...
As usual...
What a dull guy.
Hello?
Are you a student of Tsuganei High School?
Um... Yes. Yes, I am.
Are you perhaps Koumoto-san?
Yes, that's me...
I am Tomomi Hetada's mother.
She has a communicable
disease exam today.
So I arranged a day off school.
I see.
But she vanished without a word.
We've been looking for her.
But we haven't found her.
- Hungry
- Are you home, Pets?
- How are you feeling?
Um, is Pets...
I mean, Tomomi, really going to Mars?
She's going away?
Nabeta
I hope there are clues
to her whereabouts.
This is Pets' room?
It's unlike a teenage girl's, right?
She doesn't have stuffed
animals or idol posters.
Um, that's not the only thing...
This is how my husband likes it.
Even though he's never home.
Um, but Pets talked about
her dad now and then.
Did she?
I suppose she was trying to seem normal.
She's never invited friends over...
...but she spoke
of you several times.
I gave her that photo
in grade school.
I heard your
mother took this photo.
She hates taking photos,
so we don't have many in our home.
You've been friends for a long time.
Yes.
If there's anything
you know, please tell me.
Okay.
I'm sure you know where she is.
You've been in contact, right?
We haven't, really.
Please tell me!
Hey...
Why are you hiding it? Tell me...
Otherwise... Otherwise...
My husband will be...
I-I really don't know!
Ow! It hurts!
Climb in.
B-But this isn't your car...
Just climb in.
Whee! This is a V8!
V8! V8! V8! V8!
Why'd you help me?
Whoa, so self-centered!
It wasn't for you or anything.
I-I'm sorry.
No one does anything for someone else.
It's all for yourself.
I didn't know anything.
I didn't know that
I just pretended I knew.
Everything in my life...
...was made of lies.
Commu-Center.
Post-Graduation Questionnaire
She never turned it in.
Wait... Hold on...
N-No way...
Wait... Let me go!
W-What's going on?
I found it!
P-Pets!
K-Kana-bun.
Dammit!
Pets!
Jeez! What is this?
It won't come off!
Why you...
Hold on, okay?
I'm gonna help you!
Kana-bun...
Jeez! What's with this?
Confirmed the target.
It's the terminal core.
What'll we do? Can we stop it?
I'll do what I can. If so,
it'll be just for a few seconds.
Huh? What's the point?
There isn't any.
I'll leave the rest to you.
The artificial island! Head there!
If only I had the master cannon...
Kana-bun! You okay?
Huh?
Horrible cavities.
Early prevention is key.
Damn you!
Pets, is it true
you're going to Mars?
I won't ever see you again?
I'm sorry...
Why... Why didn't you tell me?
Because...
And I had no clue about your family.
I thought we were friends...
If something's
bothering you, let me know!
Don't keep it to yourself!
Aren't we friends?
We've been together a long time!
You're annoying.
Really annoying.
What's with you? This friend
stuff is really annoying.
I can't take it.
Why don't you just get it?
Like the time with Hijiri.
Just because we're friends?
You just butt in.
You're just a busybody!
With Mossan, too.
You should've left her alone.
She told you to, right?
Yet you felt hurt?
Things didn't work out, right?
What's with that?
You're a real pain!
S-Sorry...
Don't apologize!
What'll that do?
Like with Sasaki, too!
There was a time I was interested in him.
But since you liked him, I didn't say
anything! Don't talk down to me!
I-I didn't...
Shut up! Don't talk!
I'm asking you not to talk!
I don't know why I
talked to you back then...
I don't know why... I became
friends with someone like you.
Wait...
Please wait!
Yikes.
What power...
Not bad.
Koumoto-san.
Wanna walk together,
Koumoto-san?
S-Sure.
It's Hetada-san, right?
Call me Pets.
Pez? Like the candy?
No, with a "t" in it.
Since Hetada has one.
Oh, okay. Wait, what?
Do you have a nickname?
Not really...
Okay, hold on.
"Kana Koumoto," right?
So...
Kana-bun! Kana-bun! Kana-bun!
Are you all right, Kana-bun?
The beach?
What were you doing?
You're such a handful.
S-Sorry.
I'm the one at fault.
Forget that stuff.
Yeah, she's not going anymore.
She decided not to migrate.
She wants to hang
with us some more.
R-Really?
Pets...
Sorry for keeping quiet about leaving
and saying those mean things.
It's okay. It's okay!
Kana-bun... We'll always
be together from now on.
Yeah.
Like I said,
I'm a government employee.
That hag just isn't
answering the phone.
You're going?
Is that okay with you?
I said we're under construction!
Ow. Ow...
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait...
Dammit...
Don't get in my way!
You're pretty good.
High school girls
are so complicated.
Computing estimated
plant startup time.
Startup in approximately
34 hours and 43 minutes.
Hello?
Less than two days before startup.
It's the same all over the world.
Oh? I plan on getting
on a 5:00 p.m. flight tomorrow.
Sounds like you're going on a trip.
It's a trip of sorts.
A Mars tour with select emigrants.
Oh, I wonder
if Mars has hot springs?
Thanks for your hard work.
Are you listening?
Everyone's just
thinking of themselves...
What's first period?
Math? Though I'm
sure it'll be self-study.
Shouldn't they just close school?
Probably.
But if they did,
there's nothing to do.
We could go to Kana's place.
She's been out a while.
I guess we should
give her some space, huh?
Regional Unrest, Government on Alert
Bunta, change the channel.
They're all the same.
Just showing reruns.
Sis!
Feeling better, Kana?
Yeah. I'm going out for a bit.
To where?
Work.
You could've taken the day off.
There aren't many customers.
They're saying the world's ending.
Though I'll keep making
soba here till the end.
Here you go!
Thank you for waiting.
I believe... I ordered cold soba.
But that's your usual order.
I felt like eating
cold noodles today.
I'm sorry, but...
Why not keep it the same?
Keep what?
Why can't it be
like it's always been?
I want things to be
as they've always been.
Keep things the same, huh?
It's so hot! I'm so sluggish.
We should've ditched.
Wanna grab a bite?
Nothing's open.
Yeah, probably.
So lame.
An adult pretending
to be a high school punk?
I'm neither.
Did you smoke before?
I wasn't able to quit.
What's with you?
Man, my back hurts.
You're getting old.
Aliens don't age.
I'm 19 today and tomorrow.
Tomorrow, huh.
I first tried smoking when
I was 17, during summer.
Adolescence...
I never imagined
I'd end up like this...
That's gloomy...
Yeah.
I kinda feel like
shooting up some fireworks...
...but just the two
of us wouldn't be fun.
Yeah.
Do you have a light?
Okay! Let's take roll!
Oh, big one.
Like I'm shedding skin?
As expected...
That was a long walk.
My feet are gonna fall off. And stink.
Hey.
The ocean is big and vast.
I don't remember
the lyrics after that.
That's awful.
Wait. How'd it go?
The moon rises and the sun sets.
That's it! And the last part?
There's more to it?
I'm sure there is.
I want to go to another country.
Hey, Pets! Have a nice trip!
Take care!
See you! Don't forget about us!
Go, go, go, go!
Wait up, Mossan!
The sparkling ocean
burns into memory.
We're unable to fly
as the day ends.
I knew for a long time.
I knew, but I
pretended not to notice.
I thought if I pretended long
enough, it would stay the same.
But...
Huh?
Aw, they left.
I wonder what Mars
is like. Is it fun?
I dunno. I would've liked to go.
I...
There you are!
Oops.
Hey, this isn't
the time to be napping!
Haruko-san?
Why?
Explanations later.
It's time...
Hurry, Raharu!
What? It's moving?
What'll happen now?
I don't like bad endings.
With me and her...
...we'll send it flying!
A few hours later
Fly?
Yeah, to Mars.
We don't know how many
we can actually transfer.
But even if there's a small chance...
Kana-bun's N.O.
Yeah.
If it's Kana Koumoto's power...
...that can wipe out
an immense mecha in a flash...
Well, I don't care how it's done...
I won't let it end this way.
Yeah. Let's do all we can.
Acting cool all of a sudden...
I'm a boring guy just
struggling for survival.
Then show me your best struggle.
Well...
It's time to make them yelp!
Ow...
The school!
What? No way!
Is this okay?
Your city is going away.
Only your forehead
can do something.
You gonna stay quiet and watch?
Things don't stay the same forever.
You know that's impossible.
The city and its
surroundings change. We all age.
Precious things disappear.
But since they do,
why not have the same smile as always?
- But how should I...
I dunno. I'm not you.
Kana...
You're going to battle that thing?
You look ready.
I love my friends!
She's shouting?
Not just my friends!
I love everyone!
Nice. Give 'em
everything you've got.
You showed. But it
won't be like before...
This is getting fun.
Outnumbered thirty to one!
This is getting ridiculous!
Hey, don't stand there!
Hurry up and let 'em have it!
I-I love everyone!
They're important to me!
I love spending time with them!
Oh, I said love again...
I don't have a dream for my future!
I don't know what I want yet...
I wanted things to stay
the same forever...
I didn't want to believe
things would end...
I knew that
it wouldn't last forever...
But I didn't want to believe it...
Still... That doesn't mean...
Um, I'm not saying it right...
Why?
Jeez! Are you still worried
about what others think?
Shout it out, 17 year old!
The exotic reaction...
What's that?
She looks so cool...
I was always alone.
I longed to have friends.
I didn't want to be by myself.
I was scared
of not being liked...
So I was sensitive
to what others thought...
Ended up butting in...
Yet I relied on others...
Got into fights...
Just went in circles!
Created a persona!
Moved with the flow! Was annoying!
But I know all that!
And now I'm not
scared of not being liked!
We're floating!
Did I lose weight?
It's anti-gravitational force!
Why, Pets?
Why did you leave?
We never made up...
I never said goodbye!
What's that?
Whoa.
The naked... focal point!
This is outside the scope
of our calculations!
At this rate,
space-time itself will...
This is horrible, Pets!
Let me thank you!
Let me at least say goodbye!
After all, we're friends!
I-It's so lonely, Pets...
I'm lonely...
So lonely...
But...
Even so, I like it here...
I'm staying here as always...
...and walking in this city.
Pets!
I love you!
Bye, Mom!
See you later!
Every day is drifiting
in a pink light.
It's too bright for eyes swollen from crying,
and my head really hurts...
But the familiar view
is somehow novel.
Even if tomorrow's
a gathering of yesterdays...
...I will...
in this city...
Kana!
Morning!